cyberbully411.com 2014-03-26

# Privacy Policy « Stop Cyber Bullying

## Privacy Policy

Prevent Cyber Bullying is a free web site with Internet safety information. When you visit our Web site, we do not collect any information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us (other than information automatically collected and stored in the Web server’s logs—see below). Prevent Cyber Bullying links to other Web sites as a service to you, and once a you leave the Prevent Cyber Bullying site to visit a linked site, the privacy policy of that site applies.

**Personal Information**

You do not have to provide any personal information to visit this Web site.

If you choose to provide us with information about yourself through an e-mail message, form, survey, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication.

**Information Automatically Collected and Stored in Web Server Logs**

When you browse through any Web site, certain personal information about you can be collected. Our Web server software automatically collects and temporarily stores the following information about each visit for statistical purposes:

  * the name of the domain you use to access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are using an America Online account, or stanford.edu, if you  
are connecting from Stanford University’s domain)
  * the date and time of the visit
  * the pages visited
  * the address of the Web site you came from when you came to visit

We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make ournsite more useful to visitors. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.

**Disclosure**

Prevent Cyber Bullying does not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information about visitors, unless required for law enforcement or by statute.

**Intrusion Detection**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.
